{
    "subject": "resource/Death_at_a_Funeral_(2010_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ron_Glass",
    "human_readable": "Ron Glass stars in the 2010 film Death at a Funeral.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9264028072357178,
            "question": "What role did Ron Glass play in 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.925478458404541,
            "question": "Who starred in the 2010 film 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7631556391716003,
            "question": "What film did Ron Glass star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6651523113250732,
            "question": "Name a film starring Ron Glass."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229560375213623,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'Death at a Funeral' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5605188608169556,
            "question": "Is Ron Glass known for acting in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5525240302085876,
            "question": "Can you name another actor who starred in 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5392306447029114,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47971153259277344,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3571249544620514,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or remakes of 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ron Glass stars in the 2010 film Death at a Funeral.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2945_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2945_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2945_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another actor who starred in 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2945_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2945_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention Ron Glass's roles and films, but there is no specific mention of him starring in the 2010 film \"Death at a Funeral\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Ron Glass appeared in the movie \"Death At A Funeral\" (2010), which supports the statement that he stars in the 2010 film \"Death at a Funeral.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information states that Ron Glass had roles in more than a dozen movies including Death At A Funeral (2010), but it does not specify that he starred in it, only that he was involved.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}